{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Question Number 1",
      "variants": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variant 1 (right)"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Variant 2"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Variant 3"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Variant 4"
        }
      ],
      "rightVariantId": ["A"]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Question Number 2",
      "variants": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variant 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Variant 2 (right)"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Variant 3"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Variant 4"
        }
      ],
      "rightVariantId": ["B"]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Question Number 3",
      "variants": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variant 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Variant 2"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Variant 3 (right)"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Variant 4"
        }
      ],
      "rightVariantId": ["C"]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Question Number 4",
      "variants": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variant 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Variant 2"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Variant 3"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Variant 4 (right)"
        }
      ],
      "rightVariantId": ["D"]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Question Number 5",
      "variants": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variant 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Variant 2"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Variant 3"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Variant 4 (right)"
        }
      ],
      "rightVariantId": ["D"]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Question Number 6",
      "variants": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variant 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Variant 2"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Variant 3 (right)"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Variant 4"
        }
      ],
      "rightVariantId": ["C"]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Question Number 7",
      "variants": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variant 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Variant 2 (right)"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Variant 3"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Variant 4"
        }
      ],
      "rightVariantId": ["B"]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Question Number 8",
      "variants": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variant 1 (right)"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Variant 2"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Variant 3"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Variant 4"
        }
      ],
      "rightVariantId": ["A"]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Question Number 9",
      "variants": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variant 1 (right)"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Variant 2"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Variant 3"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Variant 4"
        }
      ],
      "rightVariantId": ["A"]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Question Number 10",
      "variants": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variant 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Variant 2 (right)"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Variant 3"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Variant 4"
        }
      ],
      "rightVariantId": ["B"]
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Question Number 11",
      "variants": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variant 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Variant 2"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Variant 3 (right)"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Variant 4"
        }
      ],
      "rightVariantId": ["C"]
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Question Number 12",
      "variants": [
        {
          "id": "A",
          "text": "Variant 1"
        },
        {
          "id": "B",
          "text": "Variant 2"
        },
        {
          "id": "C",
          "text": "Variant 3"
        },
        {
          "id": "D",
          "text": "Variant 4 (right)"
        }
      ],
      "rightVariantId": ["D"]
    }
  ],
  "gifts": [
    {
      "id": 12,
      "numberOfRightAnswers": 12,
      "gift": "$1000000"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "numberOfRightAnswers": 11,
      "gift": "$500000"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "numberOfRightAnswers": 10,
      "gift": "$250000"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "numberOfRightAnswers": 9,
      "gift": "$125000"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "numberOfRightAnswers": 8,
      "gift": "$64000"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "numberOfRightAnswers": 7,
      "gift": "$32000"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "numberOfRightAnswers": 6,
      "gift": "$16000"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "numberOfRightAnswers": 5,
      "gift": "$8000"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "numberOfRightAnswers": 4,
      "gift": "$4000"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "numberOfRightAnswers": 3,
      "gift": "$2000"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "numberOfRightAnswers": 2,
      "gift": "$1000"
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "numberOfRightAnswers": 1,
      "gift": "$500"
    }
  ]
}
